//-------------------------Set 1-----------------------
final List<Map<String, String>> questions = [
  {"question": "", "answer": ""},
  {"question": "Identify the person ?", "answer": "Gehendra Samsher"},
  {
    "question": "Tdentify the real name of this person ?",
    "answer": "Edson Arentes do Nascimento"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give the scientific name of the given plant?",
    "answer": "Brassica campestris"
  },
  {"question": "Identify the person name?", "answer": "Sanduk Ruit"}
];

//-------------------------Set 2-----------------------
// final List<Map<String, String>> questions = [
//   {"question": "", "answer": ""},
//   {"question": "Identify the person ?", "answer": "Gehendra Samsher"},
//   {
//     "question": "Tdentify the real name of this person ?",
//     "answer": "Edson Arentes do Nascimento"
//   },
//   {
//     "question": "Give the scientific name of the given plant?",
//     "answer": "Brassica campestris"
//   },
//   {"question": "Identify the person name?", "answer": "Sanduk Ruit"}
// ];
